Do you know what I have done? I bought some Axfood shares.
Vet du vad jag har gjort? Jag köpte lite Axfood-aktier.
-Axfood? What can you do about Axfood? -I got tips from a share expert.
-Axfood? Vad kan du om Axfood? -Jag fick tips av en aktieexpert.
Wait. Before you invested did you read well?
Vänta. Innan du investerade läste du väl på?
No, I didn't read on myself. I got tips from a stock expert as well.
Nej, jag läste inte på själv. Jag fick tips av en aktieexpert liksom.
Do you understand what you have done?! You have to keep track of P/E ratios, valuation, dividend!
Fattar du vad du har gjort?! Du måste ha koll på P/E-tal, värdering, utdelning!
-You need to know what does before you invest. -Sid, sorry, sorry.
-Du måste veta vad gör innan du investerar. -Förlåt, förlåt, förlåt.
What then sorry? Now you come along!
Vad då förlåt? Nu följer du med!
-What is going on? -Okay. You bought the Axfood share.
-Vad är det som händer? -Okej. Du har köpt Axfood-aktien.
Now gasoline prices have risen. Then there will be worse margins.
Nu har bensinpriserna stigit. Då blir det sämre marginaler.
It costs more to deliver to and from the stores. The share falls 10 %.
Det kostar mer att leverera till och från butikerna. Aktien faller 10 %.
What are you doing? A. buys more. B. sells everything. C. retains.
Vad gör du? A. Köper mer. B. Säljer allt. C. Behåller.
-I do not know. -How you can't know?!
-Jag vet inte. -Hur kan du inte veta?!
You have to count on it! You need to know what you do before you buy shares.
Du måste ju räkna på det! Du måste veta vad du gör innan du köper aktier.
Sorry. I would only buy one share. It would go up and I sell with a profit.
Förlåt. Jag skulle bara köpa en aktie. Den skulle gå upp och jag sälja med vinst.
Okay. We turn it on. Axfood beats expectations.
Okej. Vi vänder på det. Axfood slår förväntningarna.
Profit and growth will be 7 and 5 % better than expected.
Vinsten och tillväxten blir 7 respektive 5 % bättre än väntat.
The share rises 3 %. What are you doing now?
Aktien stiger 3 %. Vad gör du nu?
A. buys more. B. sells everything. C. retains.
A. Köper mer. B. Säljer allt. C. Behåller.
3 % up? I keep. I do not know.
3 % upp? Jag behåller. Jag vet inte.
-C. I keep. -Why do you do it?
-C. Jag behåller. -Varför gör du det?
Please, I don't know. Sorry. I have no idea.
Snälla, jag vet inte. Förlåt. Jag har ingen aning.